moneymako.com 2012-04-02

# MoneyMako - Privacy Policy

The following points mentioned herein below outlines the terms and conditions of usage of this website and the privacy policies under which we may use any data that we collect from you. The terms and conditions and the privacy policies mentioned herein are subject to change from time to time. You are requested to review the same when you are using the website.

#### Collection of Information and its Usage

It is imperative to collect certain data for the smooth functioning of the website and also to ensure that we are able to provide you with the required quality of service that we promise. Such information includes but are not limited to information regarding your visits to MoneyMako, any information that you may have used during your usage like traffic data, location data, weblogs and any communication that you may have with other members or with us through the communication channels on the website. 

Any form filled up by you enables us to collect data regarding your registration details and any purchases made by you on the website. 

Any information thus collected will enable us to provide a better service to you. The same is also utilized: 

a) To provide information and data to you which you may have opted for on the website. 

b) We may send out specific information about products and services which we feel might be relevant to your interest and which you have specifically opted for. 

c) From time to time we may communicate with you through email to update you about any changes in terms and or policies that we have implemented and thus may affect your usage of the site. 

d) If you are an existing customer you may be contacted in connection with any past sale. 

e) We have tie-ups with a few third party companies offering specific products and services which may be unrelated to our website. We may share your information with these companies; however we will only share your information if specifically agreed by you. 

f) None of the information above which may identify you in person is shared with any third party. Although we may share demographic statistics about our site visitors with them. 

g) Moreover any information that is shared is with the explicit permission from you. All such communication will have an opt-out option and if exercised you will not be contacted in the future with such communication. 

#### Access of Information

Any information that we store relating to the financial data such as credit card and bank information and transactional information, usage of the site, unique identifier such as password and username, and communication between the user and us through the website is available upon request by the user to us. If you need any of these information, feel free to contact us on [support@moneymako.com](mailto:support@moneymako.com) and we will get in touch with you. 

#### Cookies

MoneyMako traffic analytics to measure and analyse traffic and demographic data. Such analytics systems are industry standard and are embedded on each page which collects the following simple set of information: IP address of the user, IP related information, browser type and version, Operating system, referral pages and the time stamp. This information is stored on the log files of the server and is used for the purposes of the site user analysis and for identifying the preferences of the users. This information helps us to updated and improve the content which is most visited and provide more related content to our users. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password for forums or blogs so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site.Additionally our site also uses cookies which are essentially small files and are stored in the personal computer of the user. Cookies can either session ID cookies or persistent cookies. Session ID cookies store information which expires once you close your browser, however persistent cookies are those which keeps the information even after the browser is closed out. Session cookies helps in easy navigation of the website whereas persistent cookies are used to store information such as login details etc. so that you don't have to sign-in each time you are trying to use our website. It can also help us understand your usage pattern so that we can better deliver that content which interests you. 

#### Security

We adopt and implement industry standard security measures for safeguarding the information that is shared by our users on our website. Due diligence and safety procedures as necessitated by such industry standards are complied with. However it is pertinent to understand that no form of digital security is 100% safe. As such we cannot guarantee that your information is 100% secured on our website. If you wish to know more about the security systems that we implement or how your information is stored on our servers you may contact us on [support@moneymako.com](mailto:support@moneymako.com). 

#### Links to other websites

This website may carry links to other third party websites. While we carry those we in no way are in control of the content and its accuracy or validity and the privacy policies practiced by those websites and assume no responsibility for any inconveniences caused due to the use or reliance on such information. We strongly recommend you to review the terms and conditions and privacy polices of such sites before using them. 

#### Terms and conditions

These privacy policies mentioned here in are to be read in conjugation with the terms and conditions governing the usage of this website. The same are available on the following page - [Terms and conditions](http://moneymako.com/common/common/terms_of_service). 

#### Your Consent

Your continued usage of this website is an explicit agreement conforming to the privacy policies and terms and conditions as mentioned herein. 

#### Site and Service Updates

Our site goes through changes and updations from time to time. We shall the contact the user of such changes via email. Such service emails, however cannot be unsubscribed from as they contain important information that is related to the usage of the site and the account of the user. For any enquiries which are specifically requested to be reverted by phone and for any issues relating to the users account we may also contact you through email or phone. 

#### Legal Disclaimer

Although we do not disclose any information related to your personal data to any third party without your specific and explicit permission, we remain liable by any applicable law of the land in force or any law that may come in to force; or to any investigative agency; or for complying with any judicial proceeding or court order to divulge any information which may be required by them from us. 

Further, in the event we decide to sell all or any part of our company assets to any third party we may have to also share any personal information of our users to them. 

#### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page and or the date of such modification will be mentioned below. 

This privacy policy was last modified on **April 26, 2011**. 

#### Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us by phone or postal mail, our contact information is as given below: 

164 47th Ternovskogo St.  
Penza, Russian Federation 440064 

+7-902-352-16-96
